Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Track and Cross Country
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting track and cross country
1886-1997
RU 943
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
41.25
The records consist of scrapbooks, correspondence, score cards, and publications documenting track and cross country at Yale University.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Existence and Location of Copies
Track scrapbooks are available on microfilm from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM191. 1984. 4453 frames on 5 reels, 35mm.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of scrapbooks, correspondence, score cards, and publications documenting track and cross country at Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College sports; Track and field; Scrapbooks; Yale University Athletic Association; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University -- Track and field; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics, Physical Education, and Recreation
- Scrapbooks of the track team, 1913-1956; Accession 2006-A-020
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  Patrons must use FILM HM191 instead of the originals.
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1913-1915 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
    - 1914-1917 (Box 17, Reel 1U)
    - 1917-1920 (Box 2, Reel 1U)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 3, Reel 1U)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 4, Reel 2U)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 5, Reel 2U)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 6, Folder 1, Reel 3U)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 7, Folder 2 - 3, Reel 3U)
    - 1928-1930 (Box 8, Reel 3U)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 9, Folder 4, Reel 4U)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 5 - 6, Reel 4U)
    - 1934-1938 (Box 11, Folder 7, Reel 4U)
    - 1934-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8 - 9, Reel 5U)
    - 1938-1942 (Box 13, Reel 5U)
    - 1946-1949 (Box 14, Reel 5U)
    - 1950-1954 (Box 15, Reel 5U)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 16, Reel 5U)
- Men's and women's track and cross country records, 1886-1997; Accession 2006-A-240
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
  - Cross Country
    - Cornell, 1929-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - IC4A, 1930-1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Amherst, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dartmouth, 1932-1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Princeton, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Schedules, 1934-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Awards, 1934-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Northeastern, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Penn State, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Hillhouse (Frosh), 1935, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - MIT, 1936-1940 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Wesleyan, 1936-1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Statistics, 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cheshire, 1938, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - ICAAAA, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - UConn, 1940-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - NYU, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Manhattan, 1942, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Fordham-Manhattan, 1947-1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - St. John"s, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Holy Cross, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - ICAAAA, 1949-1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Columbia, 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Brown, 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Army, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Navy, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Schedules, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Squad, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Massachusetts, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Brooklyn Prep (Frosh), 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Summaries, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Results, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Horace Mann (Frosh), 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - New Britain, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - National Collegiate Cross Country Champ, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Opponents" Results, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - ICAAAA (Outdoor), 1956-1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Alumni Mag, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Score Book, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Officials, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Brown-Conn (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Brown-Conn (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Cheshire (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Cornell (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Cornell (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Fordham (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Fordham (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Heps (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Holy Cross (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Holy Cross (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - IC4A (Frosh), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - IC4A (Varsity), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Manchester Road Race, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - NCAA, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Opponents" Results, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Disability, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Gate Lists for Football Games, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Newsletter, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Newsletter (Carbons), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Roster and Schedule, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Schedule - Other Schools, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Stencils, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Avon (Frosh), 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Brown-UConn (Frosh), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Brown-UConn (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Frosh), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Cornell (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Fordham (Frosh), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Fordham (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Frosh), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Heps (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - IC4A (Frosh), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - IC4A (Varsity), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Thanksgiving Day Road Race, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Opponents" Results, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Captains and Managers, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Disability, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Football Gate List, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Newsletter, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Publications, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Schedule - Other Schools, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Stencils, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Yale Track Association, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - NCAA, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Memorandums, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Roster and Schedule, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Brooklyn Prep, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Brown-UConn (Frosh), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Brown-UConn (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Frosh), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Cornell (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Fordham (Frosh), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Fordham (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Frosh), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Heps (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - IC4A (Frosh), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - IC4A (Varsity), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Opponents" Results, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Disability, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Football Gate List, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Newsletter, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Roster, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Schedule - Other Schools, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Invitational, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Notices, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Avon Farms, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Brown-UConn (Frosh), 1961 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Brown-UConn (Varsity), 1961 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Cornell, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Dartmouth-Columbia, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Fordham, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Harvard-Princeton, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Heps, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - IC4A, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - NCAA, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Opponents" Results, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Correspondence and Notices, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Newsletter, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Schedules - Other Schools, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Annual Report - Yale AA, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Disability, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Roster, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Stencils, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - AAU, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Brown-UConn (Frosh), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Brown-UConn (Varsity), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Frosh), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth (Varsity), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - Cornell (Varsity), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Fordham (Frosh), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Fordham (Varsity), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Frosh), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Harvard-Princeton (Varsity), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Heps, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - IC4A, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Opponents" Results, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Football Gate List, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Manager"s Gate List, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Roster, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Schedules for Opponents, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Schedule - Other Schools, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Correspondence and Notices, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Disability, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - General Warning, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - NCAA, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 155)
    - Brown, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - Choate (Varsity vs. Frosh), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 157)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 158)
    - Cornell, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 159)
    - Fordham, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - Havard-Princeton, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - Heps, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - IC4A, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - UConn, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - Opponents" Results, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 165)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - Opponent"s Schedules, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 167)
    - Schedule, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - Roster, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - Brown, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - CCSU, 1964 September 22 (Box 2, Folder 171)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 172)
    - Cornell, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 173 - 174)
    - Fordham, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 175)
    - Harvard-Princeton, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 176)
    - Heps, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 177)
    - IC4A, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 178)
    - UConn, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 179)
    - Officials, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 180)
    - Schedule, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 181)
    - Brown, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 182)
    - CCSU Practice Run, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 183)
    - Columbia (Frosh), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 184)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 185)
    - Cornell, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 186)
    - Fordham, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 187)
    - Harvard-Princeton, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 188)
    - Heps and Columbia Invitational, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 189)
    - NCAA, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 190)
    - IC4A, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 191)
    - UConn, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 192)
    - Notices, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 193)
    - Opponents" Schedules and Results, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 194)
    - Donovan, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 195)
    - Army, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 196)
    - Brown, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 197)
    - CCSU-Wesleyan Practice Run, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 198)
    - Columbia (Frosh), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 199)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 200)
    - Cornell, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 201)
    - Fordham, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 202)
    - Harvard-Princeton, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 203)
    - Heps and Columbia Invitational, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 204)
    - IC4A, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 205)
    - Navy, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 206)
    - NCAA, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 207)
    - NCTCA, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 208)
    - Princeton, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 209)
    - Southern Connecticut State-St. John"s (Frosh), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 210)
    - UConn, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 211)
    - Brochure, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 212)
    - Disability, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 213)
    - Awards, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 214)
    - General, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 215)
    - Prep School, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - AAU, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 217 - 218)
    - Army, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 219 - 220)
    - BAA, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Boston Knights of Columbus, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 222 - 223)
    - Brown, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Cleveland Knights of Columbus, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Columbia (Frosh), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Columbia-CCSU (Frosh), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Connecticut Intercollegiate Relays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Cornell, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 230 - 231)
    - Connecticut AAU, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Dartmouth, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Federation Invitation, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - Fordham, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Harvard (Outdoors), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Harvard-Princeton, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 237 - 238)
    - Heps, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 239 - 240)
    - Heps (Outdoor), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - IC4A, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 242 - 243)
    - IC4A (Outdoor), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Kansas Relays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Madison Square Garden, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Marine Corps Relays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Millrose, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - NCAA, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 249 - 250)
    - NY Athletic Club, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - NYC Dev. Meets, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - NY Knights of Columbus, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Oxford-Cambridge, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 254 - 255)
    - Pan-American Games, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Penn, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Penn Relays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Penn-Brown, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Philadelphia Classic, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Practice Meet, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 261 - 262)
    - Princeton, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - Princeton (Outdoor), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Queens-Iona Relays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - St. John"s-Rutgers, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Tufts Invitational Relays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - UConn, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - Admissions, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 269)
    - Athletic Association Awards, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - Disability, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    - Eligibility, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Heps Leaders, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    - Indoor Track Schedule, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 274)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - Outdoor Newsletter, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    - Records, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    - Roster, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 278 - 279)
    - Spring Trip, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Schedule, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Track Dinner, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Track and Field News, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Awards, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 284 - 285)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Mailing List Extras, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - Massachusetts Knights of Columbus, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - Newsletter, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - AAU (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Albany (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Amherst, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Army (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - BAA, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 295)
    - BC Relays, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 296 - 297)
    - Brown, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - Brown-Penn (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - Cleveland Knights of Columbus, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - Columbia (Frosh), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - Columbia-Dartmouth, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - Columbia-CCSU-SCSU (Frosh, Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - Cornell, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - Cornell (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 305)
    - Dartmouth (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - Federation, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Florida Dual, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    - Florida Relays, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    - Florida-Richmond, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    - Fordham, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    - Harvard (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - Harvard-Princeton, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - Heps, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    - Heps (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - Heps (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    - Holy Cross-CCSU (Frosh), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 317)
    - IC4A, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - IC4A (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - IC4A (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - Kentucky Relays, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - Mets, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - Millrose, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 323 - 324)
    - NCAA, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 325 - 326)
    - NCAA (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    - NYAC, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - NYAC (Indoor), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - NY Knights of Columbus, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    - Penn, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - Penn Relays, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - Practice Meet, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - Practice Run, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - Princeton, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - Queens-Iona Relays, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - St. John"s-Rutgers, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - South Carolina, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - UConn, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - All Ivy, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - Banquet, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - Barton, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - "Cap" Haralson Award, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - Class Cuts, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - Eligibility, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 346)
    - Gieg Summer, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 347)
    - Heps Games Coaches Association
    - Heps Leaders (Indoor and Outdoor), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - IC4A Track Coaches" 50th Anniversary, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - Info Office, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 350)
    - NCAA News, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - NCAA Rules, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - New England Association, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - Newsletter, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - Notices, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 355)
    - Olympic Trials, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 356)
    - Opponents" Schedules, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 357)
    - Performance (Outdoor), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 358)
    - Races and Championships, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 359)
    - Results, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 360 - 361)
    - Roster, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 362 - 363)
    - Schedule, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 364)
    - Track Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 365)
    - Yale AA Newsletter, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 366)
    - Federation, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 367)
    - Fordham, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 368)
    - Awards, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 369)
    - Coaches Association, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 370)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 371)
    - Officials, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 372)
    - Results, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 373)
    - Roster, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 374 - 375)
    - Schedules, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 376)
    - Fordham, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 377)
    - Procedures, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 378)
    - Results, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 379)
    - Summaries, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 380)
    - Roster, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 381)
    - Results, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 382)
    - Brown, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 383)
    - Brown, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 384)
    - Address Labels for Dean"s Office, undated (Box 5, Folder 385)
    - Captain, undated (Box 5, Folder 386)
    - Christmas Vacation Workouts, undated (Box 5, Folder 387)
    - Manager Checklist, undated (Box 5, Folder 388)
    - Notices, undated (Box 5, Folder 389)
    - Publicity, undated (Box 5, Folder 390)
    - Summer Schedule, undated (Box 5, Folder 391)
  - Track
    - Men"s Records
    - General, 1886-1929 (Box 6, Folder 392)
      - Princeton, 1896-1940 (Box 6, Folder 393)
      - Track Association Record Book (Vol. 1), 1909-1923 (Box 6, Folder 394)
      - Meets, 1910-1920 (Box 6, Folder 395)
      - History of Yale Track, 1919-1939 (Box 6, Folder 396)
      - Meets
        - 1926-1927 (Box 6, Folder 397)
        - 1928-1929 (Box 6, Folder 398)
        - 1934-1935 (Box 6, Folder 398A)
      - Expenses, 1930-1936 (Box 6, Folder 399)
      - Correspondence, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 400)
      - General, 1930-1940 (Box 6, Folder 401)
      - ICAAAA Meeting Reports, 1934-1940 (Box 6, Folder 402)
      - Heps, 1935, 1954-1962 (Box 6, Folder 403)
      - Correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 6, Folder 404)
      - Results, 1937, 1952-1960 (Box 6, Folder 405)
      - General, 1939-1949 (Box 6, Folder 406)
      - Scores, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 407)
      - Scorecards, 1949-1953 (Box 6, Folder 408)
      - Scores, 1950-1954 (Box 6, Folder 409)
      - Brochures, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 410)
      - Summaries, 1950-1958 (Box 6, Folder 411)
      - General, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 412)
      - Entry Blanks, 1952-1957 (Box 6, Folder 413)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1962 (Box 6, Folder 414)
      - Scorecards, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 415)
      - Scores, 1955-1958 (Box 6, Folder 416)
      - Miscellaneous, 1955-1962 (Box 6, Folder 417)
      - General, 1956-1963 (Box 6, Folder 418)
      - Ray Tompkins
        - 1955-1956 (Box 7)
        - 1956-1957
        - 1958
        - 1959
      - General, 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 419)
      - Entry Blanks, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 420)
      - Harvard-Princeton, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 421)
      - Harvard-Princeton, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 422)
      - Newsletter, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 423)
      - Rules, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 424)
      - Summaries, 1962-1969 (Box 6, Folder 425)
      - Oxford-Cambridge, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 426)
      - New Haven, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 427)
      - Newsletter and Track Association, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 428)
      - Projects - Managers, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 429)
      - Record Applications - AAU, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 430)
      - Roster, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 431)
      - Training Table, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 432)
      - Millrose, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 433)
      - New Haven Track and Field Club, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 434)
      - Notices, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 435)
      - Roster, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 436)
      - Brochures, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 437)
      - AAU Development Meets, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 438)
      - AAU Events, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 439)
      - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 440)
      - Mottley, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 441)
      - NCAA, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 442)
      - NY Knights of Columbus, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 443)
      - Newsletters, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 444)
      - Olympic Games Committee, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 445)
      - Opponents, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 446)
      - Opponents" Results, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 447)
      - Opponents" Schedules, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 448 - 449)
      - Peace Corps, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 450)
      - Penn Relays, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 451)
      - Penn-Brown, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 452)
      - Philadelphia Inquirer Games, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 453)
      - Photos, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 454)
      - Princeton, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 455)
      - Publicity, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 456)
      - Schedule, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 457)
      - Spring Vacation, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 458)
      - Summer Meets, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 459)
      - Notices, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 460)
      - Officials, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 461)
      - Spring Trip, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 462 - 463)
      - Table, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 464)
      - Brochures, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 465)
      - Harvard, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 466)
      - IC4A, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 467)